卧槽 她居然背叛了蹭蹭
Damn! She double-crossed Snuzzles!
安静 我要好好享受
Silence! I'm going to enjoy this.
让我们衷心感谢Rick Sanchez
ANNOUNCER: Let's give a huge thanks to Rick Sanchez
感谢他除掉了灭世者 举办了这样一个酷炫的派对
for killing Worldender, putting this awesome party together,
而且请来了最火辣的天才之一
and for booking one of the hottest talents out there --
- Logic - 噢 耶
-Logic! -LOGIC: Aw, yeah.
- 瞧瞧这阵势 - 要开始了哦
-Look at that. -LOGIC: It's going down.
天哪 我肯定策划了一整个派对
Geez, I must have planned a whole party.
- *这里是Logic 大家好* - 还请了一大堆人
-LOGIC: It's Logic, y'aII. -Invited a bunch of people.
- 还不错 酒鬼Rick 还不错 - *向我的兄弟Rick致敬*
- Not bad, Drunk Rick, not bad.- Shout out to my boy, Rick.
*准备好了吗*
Are you ready?
*吭哧吭哧火车人*
There's a choo-choo train man,
*他转动着悲剧*
he's rolling down tragedy
*人人皆知超新星反抗重力*
Everybody knowing Supernova fights gravity.
- Rick 超新星要逃跑了 - 呃 谁在乎啊
-Rick, Supernova's getting away. -Eh, who cares?
可是 她刚刚想要杀我们啊
But...she was trying to kill us.